- Okay, well, make yourself at home.
- Okay.
(Penny:)- Thank you.
- You're very welcome.
[MOUTHS]
You're very welcome.
(Penny:)This looks like some serious stuff.
Leonard, did you do this?
(Sheldon:)Actually, that's my work.
(Penny:)Wow.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, well, it's just some
quantum mechanics...
(Sheldon:)...with a little string theory doodling
around the edges. That part's just a joke.
It's a spoof of the Born-Oppenheimer
approximation.
(Penny:)So you're, like, one of those
Beautiful Mind genius guys.
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(Penny:)This is really impressive.
(Leonard:)I have a board, if you like boards.
This is my board.
(Penny:)Holy smokes.
If by "holy smokes," you mean
a derivative restatement of the stuff...
(Sheldon:)...you can find scribbled on the wall
of any men's room at MIT, sure.
(Penny:)- What?
- Oh, come on.
(Sheldon:)Who hasn't seen this differential below
"here I sit brokenhearted"?
At least I didn't have to invent 26
dimensions just to make the math come out.